Guide to the Gerard Salton papers
Salton, Gerard papers
- Series IV. Professional Papers Writings Books
  - Hillman D.J. - Math. Classification Techniques (Elsinore) (Box 41, Folder 68)
  - Hillman D.J. - The Notion of Relevance (Box 41, Folder 69)
  - Hillman D.J. - On Concept-Formation and Relevance (Lehigh University) (Box 41, Folder 70)
  - Hillman D.J. - On Grammars and Category Mistakes (Box 41, Folder 71)
  - Hillman D.J. - On Quality Classes (Box 41, Folder 72)
  - Hillman D.J. - Two Models for Retrieval System Design (Box 41, Folder 73)
  - Hillman D.J. - The Measurement of Simplicity (Box 41, Folder 74)
  - Hillman D.J. - The Probability of Induction (Box 41, Folder 75)
  - Hillman D. - Prototype Retrieval System Development within an Information Resource Lab (Box 41, Folder 76)
  - Hillman D.J. - Study of Theories - Problems No.1 (Box 41, Folder 77)
  - Hillman D.J. - Study of Theories - Boolean Algebra No.2 (Box 41, Folder 78)
  - Hillman D.J. - Study of Theories - Special Classification No.3 (Box 41, Folder 79)
  - Hillman D.J. - Study of Theories - New Foundations No.4 (Box 41, Folder 80)
  - Hillman D.J. - Study of Theories - Retrieval Systems for Non-Static Document Collections No.6 (Box 41, Folder 81)
  - Hillman D.J. - Document Retrieval Theory - Arithmetization of Syntactic Analysis No.5 (Box 41, Folder 82)
  - Hillman D.J. - Study of Theory - Graphs and Algorithms for Term Relations No.7 (Box 41, Folder 83)
  - Hillman D.J. - Study of Theory - Structure of Document Relations No.8 (Box 41, Folder 84)
  - Hillman D.J. - Study of Theory - Topology and Document Retrieval Operations No.9 (Box 41, Folder 85)
  - Hillman D.J. - Document Retrieval Theory - Microcategorization for Text-Processing No.3 (Box 41, Folder 86)
  - Hillman D.J., Reed D.M. - Document Retrieval Theory - Canonical Decomposition No.4 (Box 41, Folder 87)
  - Hingston D. - Anwendung von Künstlicher Intelligenz (KI). Neue Chancen für Wirtschaftsunternehmen (Box 41, Folder 88)
  - Hirschberg, Lydia - Discussions sur l'Hypothese de Projectivite (Box 41, Folder 89)
  - Hirschberg, L. - L'utilization de l'Information semantique dans le choix des unites lexicales dans les microglossaires (Box 41, Folder 90)
  - Hirschberg, L -Biography (Box 41, Folder 91)
  - Hirschberg, Lydia - Punctuation & Automatic Syntactic Analysis (Box 41, Folder 92)
  - G. Hirst - Anaphora in Natural Language Understanding (Box 41, Folder 93)
  - Computer History (Box 41, Folder 94)
  - R. Hjerppe - Electronic Publishing (Box 41, Folder 95)
  - R. Hjerppe & B. Olander - Artificial Intelligence & Cataloging (Box 41, Folder 96)
  - Hobbs, Jerry R. - A Model for Natural Language Semantics Part I: The Model (Box 41, Folder 97)
  - Hochgesang, Guy T. - Soccer - A Concordance Program (Box 41, Folder 98)
  - Hodes, Louis - Selection of Descriptors According to Discrimination and Redundancy (Box 41, Folder 99)
  - D.A. Hoeltzel & W.H. Chieng - Pattern Matching Syntehsis as an Automated Approach to Mechanism design (Box 41, Folder 100)
  - Hoffman, Lance J. - Computers and Privacy: A Survey (Box 41, Folder 101)
  - Hoffman, Lance J. - Formularies - Program Controlled Privacy in Large Databases (Box 41, Folder 102)
  - D.R. Hofstadter - Artificial Intelligence (Box 41, Folder 103)
  - W.W. Holdheim Curriculum Vitae (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - L.A. Hollaar and R.L. Haskin Hardware-Based Pattern Matcher (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - L.A. Hollaar The Utah Text Retrieval Project (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - R.S. Hooper & S. Henderson "Paperless" Safe System (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - J.E. Hopcroft, Turing Machines (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - J.E. Hopcroft, Impact of Robotics on Computer Science (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Horty, John F., "A look at Research in Legal Information Retrieval" (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Howe, D., A Brief Introduction to Logic Programming (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Hoyle, W.G., On the Number of Categories for Classification (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Hoyle, W.G.: Automatic Indexing and Generation of Classification Systems by Algorithm (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Humboldt-Stiftung (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - S.M. Humphrey and N.E. Miller, Knowledge Based Indexing (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - W.J. Hutchins, Review of Analysis of Meaning (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Hutchins, W.J., Automatic Document Selection without Indexing (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Hypertext Conference Papers 1989 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Hypertext For Encyclopedia Processing (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Hypertext Operations (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Hypertext Conversation (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Hypertext and Information Retrieval, Lucarella, Fuhr (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Hypertext (Multimedia) (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - IBM Stairs System (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - "An Introduction to Information Retrieval" IBM 1960 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - IBM Corporation "General Information Manual-Keyword-in-Context (KWIC)Indexing" (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Data Processing IBM "A System for Library Catalog Card Production" (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - IBM Grant (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - IBM Justice Dept. (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Idel Kronheimer, Sun Bank (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Ide, Eleanor and Salton, Gerard, User Controlled File Organization and Search Strategies (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Ide, Eleanor, User Interaction with an Automated Information Retrieval System (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - N.M. Ide and Jean Veronis, Story Understanding (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - IHM, Peter, "Automatic Classification in Anthropology" (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Iker, H.P. and Harway, N.I., A Computer Systems Approach Towards the Recognition and Analysis of content (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - J.K. Wu and A.D. Narasimhalu, Image Retrieval (Faces) (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Image Systems (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - J.L. Bentley and B.W. Kernighan, Index Production (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Indexing Courses (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Practical ER Systems (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Info Science in Europe (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Information Science (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Information Theory (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - IR Systems on Small Machines (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Interfaces for IR (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Interface Design (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Ip, Peter H., The Formulation of Associative Retrieval in Terms of Fuzzy sets and its testing on a simulated document collection (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Isotta, N.E.C., Europe's first Info. Ret. Network (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Issaev, Lev. L. B-408, The International Nuclear Info. System (INIS): Progress Report (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - The Ithaca Yacht Club (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - T.ITO, Y.Kodama and M.Kizawa, Best Match File Searching (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - T.Ito, Similarity Measure (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - T.Ito, and M.Nakashima, Multilevel Indexed Descriptor File (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Iverson, K.E., A Method of Syntax Specification (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - K.E. Everson, A Personal View of APL (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Iverson, K.E., APL/360 (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - Iverson, K.E., "A Programming Notation for Trees" (Box 42, Folder 54)
  - Falkoff, A.D./Iverson, K.E./Sussenguth, E. "A Formal Description of System 360" (Box 42, Folder 55)
  - K.E. Iverson and R.C. Minnick, Mark IV (Box 42, Folder 56)
  - K.E. Iverson, Search Techniques (Box 42, Folder 57)
  - Iverson, K.E., Mechanism Records Meter Readings (Electrical World 9/27/54) (Box 42, Folder 58)
  - IVIE, Evan Lean: Search Procedures Based on Measures of Relatedness Between Documents (Box 42, Folder 59)
  - Jackson, D.M., The Construction of Retrieval Environments and Pseudo-Classifications Based on External Relevance (Box 42, Folder 60)
  - Jackson, D.M., A Note on a set of Functions for Information Retrieval (Box 42, Folder 61)
  - Jackson, D.M., An Error Analysis for Functions of Qualitative Attributes with Application to Info. Retrieval (Box 42, Folder 62)
  - Jackson, David, Closed Form Approx. For Random Errors in Distance Functions (Box 42, Folder 63)
  - Jackson, D.M., Research Proposal Classification Studies in Information Retrieval (Box 42, Folder 64)
  - Jackson, D.M. B-409, Stability of Classifications of Binary Attribute Data (Box 42, Folder 65)
  - Jackson, D.M., & Horotwitz, E., The Symbolic Computation of Functions of Sequences over Finite Alphabets with Given... (Box 42, Folder 66)
  - Jackson, D.M., and White, L.J., The Weakening of Taxonomic Inferences by Homological Errors (Box 42, Folder 67)
  - P.S. Jacobs, Scisor Extracting Info. From On-Line News (Box 42, Folder 68)
  - K. Sparck Jones, Early Classification Work (Box 42, Folder 69)
  - D.P. Jacobus, Chemical Coding (Box 42, Folder 70)
  - Jahoda, G. and Stursa, M.L., A Comparison of a Keyword from Title Index with a Single Access Point per Doc. Alphabetic Subject Index (Box 42, Folder 71)
  - Jain, A.K., Sampling In-Library Book Use (Box 42, Folder 72)
  - M. Jakobson, Block Accesses in Inverted Files (Box 42, Folder 73)
  - P.M. James, Product Engineering at Xerox (Box 42, Folder 74)
  - J.Janas, Recognizing Parts of Speech (Box 42, Folder 75)
  - J. Janda B-410, Trial: Info Retrieval System User's Manual (Box 42, Folder 76)
  - Japan Computers (Box 42, Folder 77)
  - Jardine, N. B-411, Automatic Document Classification & Retrieval (Box 42, Folder 78)
  - Jardine, N. and Sibson, R., The Construction of hierarchic and non-hierarchic classifications (Box 42, Folder 79)
  - N. Jardine and C.J. Van Rijsbergen, Document Classification (Collective Comparison) (Box 42, Folder 80)
  - Jardine, N. and Van Rijsbergen, Use of Hierarchic Clustering in Information Retrieval (Box 42, Folder 81)
  - Jarvis, R.A. and Patrick, Edward A., Clustering Using a Similarity Measure Based on Shared Near Neighbors (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Jeffrey, H. Joel-- A New Type of Information Retrieval System (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - K. Jenson and G.E. Heidon, Fitted Parse (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Karen Jensen, Microsoft Work on Automatic Dictionaries (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - K. Jenson and G.E. Heidorn, The Fitted Parse (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Jernigan, Richard and Alfred G. Dale, "Set Therotic Models for Classification and Retrieval" USF Rep. U. of Texas (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Johns Hopkins University, Circulaton System (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - D.E. Johnson, Design of a Robust Natural Language Interface (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Jones, Karen Sparck, Some Thoughts on Classification for Retrieval (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Jones, Karen Sparck-Automatic Thesaurus Construction and the Relation of a Thesaurus to Indexing Terms (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Jones, Karen Sparck, Automatic Term Classification and Information Retrieval (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Jones, Karen Sparck, Clumps, Theory of (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Jones, K. Sparck/Jackson, David, Current Approaches to Classification and Clump- finding at Cambridge Language Research Unit (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Jones, K.S., "Dictionary Circles" (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Jones, Karen Sparck, The Evaluation of Archaeological Classifications (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - K.Sparck Jones Intelligent Knowledge Based System (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - K.Sparck Jones, Role of Artificial Intelligence in Information Retrieval (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Karen Sparck Jones, Reflections on TREC (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - K. Sparck Jones, Info Retrieval (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - K. Sparck Jones and B.K. Boguraev, A Study of Cases (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - K. Sparck Jones, Compound Noun Interpretation (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - K. Sparck Jones, Keywork for RIAO 88 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - K. Sparck Jones, NPL Collection (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - K. Sparck Jones, Retrieving Information (Britian Library) (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - K. Sparck Jones, Bibliography January 1990 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - K. Sparck Jones, Experiments in Semantic Classification (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Jones, Karen Sparck, "Notes on Semantic Discourse Structure" (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Jones K. Sparck, "Synonymy and Semantic Classification: Ph.D. Thesis, University Of Cambridge, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Sparck Jones, K., Jackson, D.M., The Use of the Theory of Clumps for Information Retrieval (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - K. Sparck Jones, Search Term Relevance Weight (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - K. Sparck Jones and J.I. Tait, Auto Search Term Generation (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - K.S. Jones, What is an AI Experiment? (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - K. Sparck Jones, Statistical Interpretation (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - K. Sparck Jones and D.M. Jackson, Auto Keyword Classification (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Jones, G. and WISE, P.: Updating Thesaurus Classifications in Response to Data Base Changes (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - K.S. Jones, Intelligent Info Retrieval (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Jones, K. Sparck-- Report on: Automatic Indexing Workshop (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Jones, Karen Sparck, Automatic Indexing (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Jones, Karen Sparck, Does Indexing Exhaustivity Matter? (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Jones, K.S., Collection Properties Influencing Automatic Term Classification Performance (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Jones, Karen Sparck, Index Term Weighting (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - Sparck Jones, Karen, Automatic Keyword Classification for Information Retrieval (reviewed by G. Salton) (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - Jones, K.S., Collection Properties Influencing Automatic Term Classification Performance (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - K. Sparck Jones and R.G. Bates, Automatic Indexing 1976-1978 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - K.S. Jones, Statistical Bases of Relevance Assessments for Test (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - Jones, K.S., The 'Ideal' Test Collection (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - Jones, K.S., A Performance for Test Collections (Box 43, Folder 47)
  - Jones, Kevin P.; Basic Structures for Thesaural Systems (Box 43, Folder 48)
  - Jones, Paul E.; Giuliano Vincent E.; Curtice, Robert M., "Selected Collection Statistics, and Data Analyses, U.S.A.F. Feb. '67 (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - W.P. Jones and G.W. Furnas, Pictures of Relevance (Box 43, Folder 50)
  - Jones, P.E.; Giuliano, V.E.; Curtice, R.M., "Linear Models for Associate Retrieval" ESD-TR-67-202, V. II (Box 43, Folder 51)
  - P.E. Jones, V.E. Giuliano, R.M. Curtice Papers on Automatic Language Processing (Box 43, Folder 52)
  - Robert G. Jones, Syllabus for a Course in Human Communication (Box 43, Folder 53)
  - Jones, S.O., Technical Writing: A Key to Computerized Information Retrieval (Box 43, Folder 54)
  - W.T. Jones, Fuzzy Set Characterization (Box 43, Folder 55)
  - W.P. Jones Applied Use on Human Memory (Box 43, Folder 56)
  - W.P. Jones and G.W. Furnas, Pictures of Relevance (Box 43, Folder 57)
  - K. Sparck Jones, Search Term Relevance Weighting Resent Results (Box 43, Folder 58)
  - K. Sparck Jones, Statistically Document Indexing (Box 43, Folder 59)
  - K. Sparck Jones and C.A. Webster, Research on Relevance Weighting 1980 (Box 43, Folder 60)
  - K.S. Jones, Experiments on Relevance Weighting of Search Terms (Box 43, Folder 61)
  - Jonker, Frederick, et.al., "A Model Information Retrieval Network" May 1964 AF 49-(638)1209 (Box 43, Folder 62)
  - Jonker, Frederick, The Descriptive Continuum: A "Generalized" Theory of Indexing (Box 43, Folder 63)
  - Jordan, John R., Let the Computer Select Your Reading List KWIC-KWOC Index (Box 43, Folder 64)
  - A.K. Joshi, Natural Language Processing (Box 43, Folder 65)
  - Journal of Future (Box 43, Folder 66)
  - B. Karle, Wide Area Info Server (Box 43, Folder 67)
  - D. Kahn, Modern Cryptology (Box 43, Folder 68)
  - Y. Kambayashi, Equivalent Key Problem (Box 43, Folder 69)
  - Y. Kambayashi et. al., Indices for bibliographic data (Box 43, Folder 70)
  - S.M. Kannapan and K.M. Marshek, Approach to Parametric Machine Design... (Box 43, Folder 71)
  - P.B. Kantor, On Maximum Entropy Moser (Box 43, Folder 72)
  - P.B. Kantor, Logic of Weighted Queries (Box 43, Folder 73)
  - P. Kantor, Maximum Entropy (Pisa) (Box 43, Folder 74)
  - R.M. Karp, Combinatorics, Complexity and Randomness (Box 43, Folder 75)
  - Y. Kambayashi, K. Tanaka and S. Yajima, Relational Language (Box 43, Folder 76)
  - Y. Kambayashi et. al., Multi KWIC Index (Box 43, Folder 77)
  - Kaplan, Ronald, A Multi-Processing Approach to Natural Language (Box 43, Folder 78)
  - Kaplan, Ronald M., The Mind System: A Grammer-Rule Language (Box 43, Folder 79)
  - R.M. Kaplan, Lexical-Functional Grammer (Box 43, Folder 80)
  - Karlgren, Hans, Text Connexitivity and Word Frequency Distribution (Box 43, Folder 81)
  - Karlgren, Hans, Why Trees in Syntax? (Box 43, Folder 82)
  - Karlgren, Hans, Slant Grammer Calculus (Box 43, Folder 83)
  - Karlton, P.L., Fuller, S.H. et. al., Performance of Height-Balanced Trees (Box 43, Folder 84)
  - Karp, Richard, The Assembly of Address Free Programs for Bill Calculation (UT-5) (Box 43, Folder 85)
  - Amdrew J. Kasarda, A Syntactically Oriented Natural Language Document Retrieval System with a Browsability Feature (Box 43, Folder 86)
  - Kaser, David, Report of the Director of the University Libraries (Box 43, Folder 87)
  - Kasher, Asa, The Logicial Status of Indexical Sentences May 1970 (Box 43, Folder 88)
  - Kasher, Asa- Data Retrieved by Computer: A Critical Survey (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Katter, Robert V.: Language Structure and Interpersonal Commondity (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Katter, R.V.: Study of Document Representations: Mulitdimensional Scaling of Indexing Terms (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Katter, R.V. and Pearson, K.M. Medlars II: A Third Generation Bibliographic Production System (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Katz, B-Using English in Indexing (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Katz, J.J.: The Structure of a Semantic Theory (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Katz, L. and Tyas, J.P.I.-Canadian Literature on a National Policy for the Transfer of S and T Information (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Katzer, J.-Overlap Among Document Representations (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Kay, Martin-Computational Competence and Linguistic Performance (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Kay, Martin-Performance Grammars (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Kay, Martin and Su, Stanley: The Mind System: The Structure of the Semantic File (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Kaye, Jonathan: Book Indexing (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Keen, E.M.-Aberystwyth Index Language Test (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Keen, E.M.-Evaluation of Parameters (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Keen, E.M.-Measures and Averaging Methods Used in Performance Testing of Indexing Systems (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Keen, E.M., Performance of Printed Indexes (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Keen, E.M.-Performance of a Request/Document Matching Algorithms (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Keen, E.M.-Search Strategy Evaluation in Manual and Automated System (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Keen, E.M.-Term Position in Retrieval (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Keen, E.M.-User-Controlled Search (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Keen, E.M., Digger, J.A.-Report of an Information Science Index Languages Test (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Kellogg, C.H.-Inferential Question-Answering: Extending Converse (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Kellogg, Charles-Online Translation of Natural Language into Artifical Language Queries (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Kennedy, Robert A.: Mechanized Title Word Indexing of Internal Reports (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Kent, A.-Experiments in Computer-based Chemical Information Retrieval (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Kent, Allen-Information Sciences-Development of an Interdisciplinary Graduate Education Program at the University of Pittsburgh (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Kerchner-Dynamic Document Processing in Clustered Collection (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Kerchner, M.-Selective Negative Feedback Methods (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Aho, Kernighan, Weinberger-Awk Pattern Scanning (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Kermighan, B.W.-GRAP: A Language for Typesetting Graphs (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Kernighan, B.W.-PIC Graphics Language (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Kernighan, B.W. and Morgan, S.P.-Unix Operating System (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Kernighan-The Unix System-Document Preparation Tools (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Kessler, M.M.: Comparison of the Results of Bibliographic Coupling and Analytic Subject Indexing (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - King, D.W.-Comparative Evaluation of the Retrieval Effectiveness of Descriptor and Freetext Search Systems (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - King, D.W.-Bryant, E.C.-A Diagnostic Model for Evaluating Retrospective Search Systems (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Kessler, M.-Bibliographic Coupling Between Scientific Papers (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Kessler, M.M.-Experimental Study of Bibliographic Coupling between Technical Papers (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Kessler, M.M.: MIT Technical Information Project 28 March 1965 (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Kessler, M.M.-Technical Information Flow Patterns (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - Kessler, M.M. and Heart, F.E.-Concerning the Probability that a Given Paper will be Cited (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - Khatchian, L.G.-Linear Programming (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - Kilgour, Frederick-Ohio College Library Center (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - King, Donald W.-Design and Evaluation of Information Systems (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - King, Gilbert and Chang, H.-Machine Translation of Chinese (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - King Research: Communication Indicators (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - KinKade, R.G.-The Experimental Publication System: An aid to Information System Planning (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - KinKade, R.G. and Whittenburg, John A.-The Results of Operating an Experimental Publication System (Box 44, Folder 48)
  - Kirsch, Russell A.-The Application of Automata Theory to Problems in Information Retrieval (Box 44, Folder 49)
  - Kirsch, Russell A.-Computer Interpretation of English Text and Picture Patterns (Box 44, Folder 50)
  - Kirsch, Russell A.-Symposium an Automated Processing of Illustrated Text (Box 44, Folder 51)
  - Kitov, A.I. and Kerimov, S.K.-Some Problems of Machine Retrieval of Information Using Associative Programming Methods (Box 44, Folder 52)
  - Klein, S.-Automatic Paraphrasing in Essay Format (Box 44, Folder 53)
  - Klein, S.-Control of Style (Box 44, Folder 54)
  - Klein, S.-Syntactic Dependence and the Computer Generation of Coherent Discourse (Box 44, Folder 55)
  - Klein, Sheldon and Aeschlimann, John-Automatic Novel Writing (Box 44, Folder 56)
  - Klein, S. and Fabens, W.-the Autoling System (Box 44, Folder 57)
  - Klein, S. and Kuppin, M.-An Interactive, Heuristic Program for Learning Transformational Grammars (Box 44, Folder 58)
  - Klein, S. and Simmons, R.- A Computational Approach to Grammatical Coding of English Words (Box 44, Folder 59)
  - Klempner, Irving-Methodology for the Comparative Analysis of Information Storage and Retrieval Systems (Box 44, Folder 60)
  - Kling, R.-Electronic Fund Transfer (Box 44, Folder 61)
  - Kling, R.-Information Systems in Policy-Making (Box 44, Folder 62)
  - Kling, R.-Social Analysis of Computing (Box 44, Folder 63)
  - Kling, R.-Social Issues: From Arena to Discipline (Box 44, Folder 64)
  - Klingbiel, P.-Evaluation of Machine-Aided Indexing (Box 44, Folder 65)
  - Klingbiel, P.-Future of Indexing and Retrieval Vocabularies (Box 44, Folder 66)
  - Klingbiel, Paul-Machine-Aided Indexing (Box 44, Folder 67)
  - Klingemann, H.-Research and Development of Library-Style Retrieval Systems for Survey data Archives (Box 44, Folder 68)
  - Knauss, R.-Automated Industry Coding-an Artificial Intelligence Approach (Box 44, Folder 69)
  - Knauss, R.-Coding Natural Language Survey Data (Box 44, Folder 70)
  - Knauss, R.-Pattern-based Semantic Decision Making (Box 44, Folder 71)
  - Knauss-Semantic Based Decision Making (Box 44, Folder 72)
  - Knauss, R.-Similarity Measure on Semantic Network Nodes (Box 44, Folder 73)
  - Knight, G.-Classification System for Computer Abstracts on Cards (Box 44, Folder 74)
  - Knorz, G.-Air Physics Project (Box 44, Folder 75)
  - Knorz, G.-Indexing Strategy (Box 44, Folder 76)
  - Knott, G.-Balanced Tree Storage and Retrieval Algorithm (Box 44, Folder 77)
  - Barnett, Jim and Knight, Kevin-Knowledge and Natural Language Processing (Box 44, Folder 78)
  - Woodward, Brian-Knowledge Acquisition (Box 44, Folder 79)
  - Knowledge-Based Expert Systems (Box 44, Folder 80)
  - Knowledge-Based Search Tactics (Box 44, Folder 81)
  - Knowledge Representation (Box 44, Folder 82)